majorspoilers.com 2019-07-18

# Major Spoilers — Comic Book Reviews, News, Previews, and Podcasts

## Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.majorspoilers.com and Major Spoilers Entertainment, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Major Spoilers Entertainment, LLC include www.majorspoilers.com, Major Spoilers, Major Spoilers VIP and http://members.majorspoilers.com. The Major Spoilers website is a news and information and e-commerce site. By using the Major Spoilers website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Major Spoilers may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

– First and Last Name  
– E-mail Address

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Major Spoilers’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Major Spoilers collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Major Spoilers may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Major Spoilers and its affiliates.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**  
Major Spoilers does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Major Spoilers may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Major Spoilers, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Major Spoilers may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Major Spoilers or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Major Spoilers; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Major Spoilers, or the public.

**Automatically Collected Information**  
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Major Spoilers. This information can include:  your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Major Spoilers website.

**Use of Cookies**  
The Major Spoilers website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Major Spoilers pages, or register with Major Spoilers site or services, a cookie helps Major Spoilers to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Major Spoilers website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Major Spoilers features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Major Spoilers services or websites you visit.

**Registered Users**

  * If you create an account on one of our sites, you will be prompted to select a Username and provide your Email Address.
  * When choosing a Username, we strongly advise you not use or include your real name. Usernames cannot be changed.
  * Your Username and Email Address are stored in the website’s database. Your Email Address is used to send you an email with a link to set your password or to send you an email with a link to reset your password in the event you forget your password.
  * Once an account is created, you must contact us to have it deleted.
  * An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) is provided to the Gravatar service to see if a Profile picture of you is available for display. The Gravatar service privacy policy is [available here](https://automattic.com/privacy).
  * You may optionally complete your Profile by providing your First Name, Last Name, Website (URL) and/or Biographical info. These additional details are also saved in the website’s database. You may edit these details, and your Email Address, in your Profile at any time.
  * You may also choose how your name is displayed (your Display Name) to visitors to the site (e.g. in comments you create) in your Profile.
  * Your Username, First Name, Last Name and Email Address are accessible by employees on the site.
  * If you attempt to log in to our site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies at all. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
  * If you have an account and you log in to a site, we will set up several cookies to save your login information and some of your screen options. The logged-in cookies last for two days, and the screen options cookies last for a year.
  * If you select “Remember Me” these cookies will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. It is important that you log out if you are using a public computer.
  * For users that register on one of our sites, we also store the data they provide in their profile indefinitely. All registered users can see, change or delete most of that data at any time except their login name/nickname.

**Publishing Content (Comments, Pages, Posts, Forums)**

  * Your Profile Picture (Gravatar), Display Name, Website (URL) (if any) and Biographical Info (if any) may be visible to visitors to the website (e.g. if you leave a comment, forum post, or contribute an article/post).
  * If you author an article/post, your Username, User ID, Profile Picture (Gravatar), Display Name, Website (URL) (if any) and Biographical Info (if any) are provided to any visitor using the website’s REST API interface.
  * If you upload media (e.g. images) to the website (in forums, posts, or comments), you should avoid uploading images with EXIF GPS location data included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data included in images on the website.
  * Visitors using the website’s REST API interface can correlate uploaded media to a particular user. This may allow such visitors to map a user to a particular time and location if EXIF GPS location data was included in the uploaded media.
  * If you edit or publish an article/post, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
  * When visitors leave comments on one of our sites we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
  * Comments may require manual approval by one of our employees or site owners.
  * If you leave a comment on a site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies so we can recognize you as a commenter. These cookies will persist for one year.
  * Additional spam detection is provided by Automattic/Akismet. The Automattic privacy policy is [available here](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
  * Published content and comments are stored indefinitely unless deletion/removal is requested by the original author.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Embedded Content From Other Websites**

Embeds are pieces from other websites that are shown from time to time on our websites. They behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website and may use cookies or capture information. Typically embedded content is from websites that share videos, images, or other content. These services may collect your IP Address, your User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including correlating your interaction with the content with your account with that service, if you are logged in to that service.

Links to the privacy policies of the most common services have been included below. Where a general privacy policy is not available, the applicable country is indicated.

**Analytics**

We use Google Analytics for tracking visitors and aggregating information about the traffic to our websites. The Google Analytics privacy policy can be found here: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>. You can learn more about how to opt-out of tracking in [Google Analytics here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Security of your Personal Information**  
Major Spoilers secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Major Spoilers uses the following methods for this purpose:

– SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

  * For payment transactions for the Major Spoilers VIP site, we use PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).
  * To comply with accounting and legal requirements, we keep data on financial transactions on the PayPal systems.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
Major Spoilers does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**E-mail Communications**  
From time to time, Major Spoilers may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Major Spoilers or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Major Spoilers, you may opt out of such communications by unsubscribing from our email service.

**Email/Chat/Contact Forms**

  * Customers that email us, or use any of the contact forms on our websites, will have their email address, IP address, and any data provided in the contact form or body of the email.
  * The WPForms does not use cookies, and does not store any information in any of our databases.
  * You can read more about WPForms[ and their compliance here](https://wpforms.com/docs/how-to-create-gdpr-compliant-forms/).

**Marketing Campaigns**

  * We use email marketing to communicate with customers and potential customers from time to time. All email lists and campaigns are “opt-in” meaning we will not send you these sorts of emails unless you indicated that you wish to receive them during signup or other interactions on our website.
  * We may send you “system” emails, such as password reset requests or payment notifications/receipts even if you have not opted-in to email marketing lists.
  * All marketing emails sent by us will include an unsubscribe link in the footer of the email. Emails sent to you may also include standard tracking, including open and click activities.
  * We use MailChimp for our marketing and mass communication campaigns. Mailchimp’s privacy policy is found [here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

**Changes to this Statement**  
Major Spoilers reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

**Contact Information**  
Major Spoilers welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Major Spoilers has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Major Spoilers at:

Major Spoilers Entertainment, LLC  
1309 West 44th Street  
Hays, Kansas 67601

Email Address:  
podcast@majorspoilers.com

Telephone number:  
7856233493

Effective as of May 23, 2018

Cookie| Type| Duration| Description  
---|---|---|---  
No records found
